<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wisps In The Willow Trees</title>
    <description>A young trans girl writes about LGBT rights, politics, and religion.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:21:39 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:21:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:13:44 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/03/31/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/03/31/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Teacher Fired For Mentioning Her Wife</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Texas is at it again. A teacher was placed on leave in September because
one parent claimed that she had “discussed her sexuality with children.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does that mean, you ask? It means she mentioned her wife whenever talking
about her family. It’s pretty blatantly homophobic. It’s obvious a straight
woman wouldn’t get suspended from her job and “treated like a criminal” by the
school for talking about her husband.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The teacher’s name is Stacy Bailey. She was an art teacher and one of the most
loved teachers at the school by the students. Yet, because someone complained
that she was gay, she was suspended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bailey and her supporters are lobbying for greater protection for LGBT+ teachers.
There’s a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipetitions.com/petition/lgbt-protection-for-misd-employees-and-students&quot;&gt;petition&lt;/a&gt;, which I recommend any sympathetic readers sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s honestly horrifying how they are treating LGBT+ people. Texas is one of the
biggest offenders, as the Religious Right has a stranglehold on the state.
Please, support Bailey and others like her and sign the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipetitions.com/petition/lgbt-protection-for-misd-employees-and-students&quot;&gt;petition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lgbt+/news/2018/03/31/lesbian-teacher-fired-for-mentioning-wife.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lgbt+/news/2018/03/31/lesbian-teacher-fired-for-mentioning-wife.html</guid>
        
        <category>LGBT+</category>
        
        <category>lesbians</category>
        
        <category>marriage</category>
        
        
        <category>LGBT+</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Essay On LGBT+ Rights</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger Warning: Discussions of suicide, self harm, murder, assault, and rape&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Wisps in the Willow Trees.
Today’s topic is LGBT+ rights. It’s a near and dear topic, especially on today,
Transgender Visibility Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LGBT+ rights started as a movement, as far as I can identify, in the nineties.
While we still hadn’t solved the problems of sexism and racism, feminism and the
other parts of the civil rights movement had made strides (though we’re not done
yet, obviously.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humanity, as always, sucks at giving out rights. The religious oppression of
LGBT+ people has a long history, but fairly recently we won a major victory with
gay marriage being allowed. Despite this, several states are still trying to
invalidate this, such as with the South Carolina bill declaring gay marriages
“parody marriages”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, today I want to address three primary topics:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fetishization of LGBT+ individuals&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Suicide and self-harm among LGBT+ youths&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Assault (Sexual, physical, and emotional) of LGBT+ people, especially
transgender men and women.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;fetishization&quot;&gt;Fetishization&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, first off, an apology to bisexual people. You are all fetishized less
than the rest of them as far as I can see, and subject to erasure. For that,
I’d like to apologize on Humanity’s behalf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, and with a fairly well known effect, is the Fetishization of
lesbians. For some reason, straight males (and it’s usually straight males)
have a tendency to enjoy the idea of lesbians. Interestingly, even homophobes
have been known to enjoy it from a purely &lt;em&gt;ahem&lt;/em&gt; physical standpoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gay men’s &lt;em&gt;physical activities&lt;/em&gt; are often enjoyed by, as I understand,
straight women. I am less familiar with the topic, being uninterested in men
myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, and with few people being aware of it, people also fetishize
(pre-SRS) trans people, especially trans women. We are viewed as sexual objects,
the mere act of having the opposite sex’s genitalia becoming something to be
desired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ironically, all of the people so fetishized are socially entrapped by the same
thing that makes them fetishizable. Lesbians and gay men by their mere
orientation, trans men and women by their genitalia alone (see: Bathrooms).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;suicide-and-self-harm&quot;&gt;Suicide and Self-Harm&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bullying. Excused by the system, lauded by some as a “trainer” of youths,
And a horrifying practice, leading to damaged psyches. LGBT+ youths especially
are subject to it, because of the views of others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The treament of LGBT+ people wears on the psyche. Eventually, some of us break.
We try and kill ourselves. I’ve tried more then once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it’s not always other students. Sometimes, like in the case of Leelah Alcorn,
it’s the parents, the people we’re supposed to trust. In these cases, we’ll hurt
ourselves or kill ourselves because we have no one else to turn to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to keep this section short. I might expand on this in another post,
but talking about this dredges up painful memories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;assault&quot;&gt;Assault&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assault is a heavy topic. It damages the psyche and the body.
Today is the day I come out publically, but that does not mean that I have never
been bullied for being trans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been attacked, physically and emotionally, for the crimes of having long
hair and not enjoying PE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my classes, without even a word to stop it, a child threatened to “Punch any
transgender kid [he meets] in the face.” At the time, I did not realize I was
trans, but even then it cut because I knew that they were people too. Now, I am
scared for my self because children like him exist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slightly over one in four trans people will have violence commited against them.
Murder of transgender people is on the rise, with an all time high in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not to imply that the assault is limited to transgender people of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rape of lesbians is common, with some of them raped because they won’t give men
what they want. In several countries, so-called “corrective rape” occurs in
order to turn lesbians straight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All LGBT+ are attacked emotionally with damaging comments. Words like “faggot”
or “dyke”. Misgendering or deadnaming effect trans people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even in the feminist community, TERFs attack trans people, especially women,
insulting trans girls by claiming they are appropriating women’s spaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowhere is safe. I hope that someday the world will be a happy place, but with
the way things are now, that is not achievable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-you-can-do-about-it&quot;&gt;What You Can Do About It&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donate to LGBT+ charities.
Participate in pride parades.
Intervene in bullying.
Show your support for the culture.
Do whatever you can, but as always, the rule is simple:
Don’t be a bigot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;sources&quot;&gt;Sources&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Suicide_among_LGBT+_youth&quot;&gt;Wikipedia - Suicide among LGBT+ Youths&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gay_bashing&quot;&gt;Wikipedia - Gay Bashing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hrc.org/resources/violence-against-the-transgender-community-in-2018&quot;&gt;HRC - Violence against the transgender community&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lgbt+/essay/2018/03/31/an-essay-on-lgbt-rights.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lgbt+/essay/2018/03/31/an-essay-on-lgbt-rights.html</guid>
        
        <category>LGBT+</category>
        
        <category>lesbians</category>
        
        <category>transgender</category>
        
        
        <category>LGBT+</category>
        
        <category>essay</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
